Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 1 Locals, 2.
  - Local 103
    - Local 103 Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Seaman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 23, 1940; 30.
    - Local 103 Outgoing Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Margaret Toy to UE Regarding Application Blanks, June 3, 1944; 1.
      - Toy to UE Regarding Local 103 RCA Collective Bargaining, July 15, 1944; 2.
      - Toy to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization and Black Workers, September 25, 1944; 3.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Women Workers and Seniority, October 11, 1944; 4.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Organization, October 11, 1944; 5.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Finances and Dues, November 10, 1944; 6.
      - Toy to UE Regarding Local 103 Constitutions, December 12, 1944; 7.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 19, 1945; 8.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, January 19, 1945; 9.
      - Toy to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes and No Strike Pledge, April 25, 1945; 10.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with Receipt, July 2, 1945; 11.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry with Teamsters and Truck Drivers, August 17, 1945; 12.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Textile Workers, September 17, 1945; 13.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding 1945 UE Convention, December 17, 1945; 14.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 11, 1946; 15.
      - Toy to Benjamin Riskin Regarding Inter-union Rivalry with Teamsters and NLRB Elections, March 26, 1946; 16.
      - Toy to Riskin Regarding Record Industry, April 10, 1946; 17.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry with Teamsters and NLRB Elections, April 29, 1946; 18.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Finances and White Collar Workers, July 24, 1946; 19.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Finances and White Collar Workers with Receipt, September 24, 1946; 20.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 11, 1946; 21.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 5, 1946; 22.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Teamsters Local 102, November 20, 1946; 23.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, December 13, 1946; 24.
    - Local 103 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1951 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Margaret Toy to James Matles Regarding Finances and White Collar Workers with Receipt, January 3, 1947; 1.
      - Toy to Julius Emspak Regarding United Italian Aid, February 27, 1947; 2.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with Receipt, May 2, 1947; 3.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Eastern Division Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union of America, May 12, 1947; 4.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with Receipt, June 4, 1947; 5.
      - Toy to Emspak Regarding Finances and White Collar Workers with Receipt, July 2, 1947; 6.
      - Roy Wilkinson to Matles Regarding Local 103 RCA Collective Bargaining, August 3, 1943; 7.
      - Wilkinson to Emspak Regarding Second Front, September 24, 1943; 8.
      - Wilkinson to Emspak Regarding RCA Lancaster, November 16, 1943; 9.
      - Wilkinson to Emspak Regarding Guards, May 24, 1944; 10.
      - Wilkinson to Emspak Regarding Local 103 Officers, July 5, 1944; 11.
      - Arthur Wolfe to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 16, 1947; 12.
      - Wolfe to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 27, 1947; 13.
      - Wolfe to Emspak Regarding PAC, January 12, 1948; 14.
      - Progressive Shop Stewards, Division 7, Local 103 Telegram to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, September 22, 1949; 15.
      - Local 103 to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 20, 1951; 16.
    - Local 103 Salary and Expense Letters, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - John Seaman, December 13, 1940-March 5, 1941; 1-10.
      - Earl Fox, March 25-July 28, 1941; 11-26.
    - Local 103 Salary and Expense Letters, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - Earl Fox, August 19, 1941; 1-2.
      - Martin O'Grady, August 22, 1941; 3.
      - Frank Neidl, September 9-December 5,, 1941; 4-16.
      - S.M. Voltis, January 9, 1942; 17.
      - Neidl, January 9, 1942; 18.
    - Local 103 Receipts, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - John Seaman, September 8, 1938; 1.
      - Frank Steinitz, September 27, 1938; 2.
      - Seaman, October 4, 1938; 3.
      - Earl Fox, October 18, 1938; 4.
      - Seaman, November 3-December 5, 1938; 5-6.
      - Fox, December 20, 1938; 7.
      - Seaman, January 4-5, 1939; 8-9.
      - Fox, January 16, 1939; 10.
      - Seaman, February 3-September 5, 1939; 11-19.
      - Joseph Mitton, September 25, 1939; 20.
      - Seaman, September 26-December 21, 1939; 21-29.
    - Local 103 Receipts, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - John Seaman, January 10-July 16, 1940; 1-12.
      - Earl Fox, July 23-30, 1940; 13-14.
      - Seaman, August 1-5, 1940; 15-17.
      - Fox, August 12-26, 1940; 18-21.
    - Local 103 Per Capita Reports, 1938-1940, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Local 103 Stamps, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Local 103 Shipment Notices, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Joseph Mitton, December 8, 1938; 1.
      - John Seaman, December 12, 1938, March 21, 1939; 2-3.
      - Mitton, July 5, 1939; 4.
      - Seaman, September 25, 1939-June 12, 1940; 5-10.
      - Margaret Toy, June 26, 1940; 11.
      - Seaman, June 27-August 31, 1940; 12-14.
    - Local 103 Supply Requisitions, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - John Seaman, July 11-September 29, 1938; 1-3.
      - Joseph Mitton, December 5, 1938; 4.
      - Seaman, December 7, 1938-September 19, 1939; 5-10.
      - Margaret Toy, September 30, 1939; 11.
      - Seaman, October 11, 1939-June 11, 1940; 12-18.
      - Toy, June 24, 1940; 19.
      - Seaman, June 26-July 19, 1940; 20-22.
    - Local 103 Credit Bills, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Local 103 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, September 1951 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Local 103 Payment Vouchers, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - Henry Rhine, October 13-November 25, 1949; 1.
      - Edward J. Parnell, November 14-16, 1949; 2.
      - J.K. Reed, November 15-18, 1949; 3.
      - Al Boyd, November 16 and 18, 1949; 4.
      - James Crocker, November 17, 1949; 5.
      - Roberta C. Dickinson, November 17, 1949; 6.
      - Richard Grinsky, November 17, 1949; 7.
      - D.W. Rinedollar, November 17, 1949; 8.
      - Frank W. Royal, November 17, 1949; 9.
      - Fred G. Smith, November 17, 1949; 10.
      - George Stein, November 17, 1949; 11.
      - W.M. Whalen, November 17, 1949; 12.
      - D. Capaldi, November 17, 1949; 13.
      - Dominick A. Carella, November 17-18, 1949; 14.
      - Thomas J. Costello, November 17-18, 1949; 15.
      - Benjamin T. Fillari, November 17-18, 1949; 16.
      - C.J. Forrillo, November 17-18, 1949; 17.
      - S. Granato, November 17-18, 1949; 18.
      - G. Mazciandaro, November 17-18, 1949; 19.
      - Grinsky, November 19, 1949; 20.
    - Local 103 Payment Vouchers, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - Henry Rhine, March 24-May 5, 1950; 1.
      - Rhine, May 3-5, 1950; 2.
      - J. Margulis, May 12, 1950; 3.
      - Novelty Printing Company, May 15, 1950; 4.
      - Marguilis, May 16, 1950; 5.
      - Novelty Printing Company, May 17, 1950; 6.
      - James Price, May 18, 1950; 7.
      - Novelty Printing Company, May 19, 1950; 8-9.
      - Atlas Duplicating Service, May 22, 1950; 10.
      - Novelty Printing Company, May 23, 1950; 11.
      - Novelty Printing Company, May 25, 1950; 12.
    - Local 103 Lost Time Vouchers, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - N. Coriadetta, October 13, 1949; 1.
      - Dave Lipner, October 15, 1949; 2.
      - Joseph Dunn, October 17-November 9, 1949; 3-8.
      - John Cronson, November 7 and 12, 1949; 9.
      - M. Thornton, November 9, 1949; 10.
      - Dunn, November 10-12, 1949; 11-15.
      - Sylvia Blanchfield, November 14, 1949; 16.
      - Helen Dell, November 14, 1949; 17.
      - John Gray, November 14, 1949; 18.
      - Thornton, November 14, 1949; 19.
      - Irene White, November 14, 1949; 20.
      - Theodore C. White, November 14, 1949; 21.
      - J. Corretine, November 15, 1949; 22.
      - W.C. Yarrett, November 15 and 17, 1949; 23.
      - Gray, November 15, 1949; 24.
      - Thornton, November 15, 1949; 25.
    - Local 103 Lost Time Vouchers, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 73)
      - A. Boyd, November 16, 1949; 1.
      - John Gray, November 16, 1949; 2.
      - T. Moore, November 16, 1949; 3.
      - M. Thornton, November 16, 1949; 4.
      - J. Schwartz, November 16 and 18, 1949; 5.
      - E.C. Lambers, November 17, 1949; 6.
      - H. Dell, November 17, 1949; 7.
      - Gray, November 17, 1949; 8.
      - J.K. Reed, November 17, 1949; 9.
      - W.J. Van Dyke, November 17, 1949; 10.
      - Irene White, November 17, 1949; 11.
      - W.P. Reynolds, November 17, 1949; 12-13.
      - Boyd, November 17, 1949; 14.
      - Gray, November 17, 1949; 15.
      - Reed, November 18, 1949; 16.
      - Thornton, November 18, 1949; 17.
      - J. Farrell, November 19, 1949; 18.
      - B.A. Danley, November 21, 1949; 19.
      - Gray, November 21, 1949; 20.
      - P.P. Lloyd, November 21, 1949; 21.
      - Gray, November 22-28, 1949; 22-24.
      - Farrell, November 25, 1949; 25.
      - Gray, November 25, 1949; 26.
      - John Crousen, undated; 27.
      - Rocco De Felice, undated; 28.
      - Moore, undated; 29.
      - Clyde Phario, undated; 30.
      - Carl Williams, undated; 31.
    - Local 103 Micellaneous Vouchers, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 74)
      - Telephone Bill Receipt, October-November 1949; 1.
      - P. Thornton Trip to New York, January 24, 1950; 2.
      - Henry Rhine Cost of Handling Bank Account, March 24, 1950; 3.
      - Rhine Cost of Handling Bank Account, April 25, 1950; 4.
      - Postal Receipt, April 28, 1950; 5.
      - Statements of Expenses to Balitmore for Camden with Food, Hotel, and Gas Receipts, May 3-5, 1950; 6.
      - Rhine Hotel Receipt, May 4, 1950; 7.
      - Stationary Receipt, May 5, 1950; 8.
      - Dave Ratner Loan Figures, 9.
    - Local 103 Miscellaneous Financial Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 75)
      - Fred Steinitz to UE, September 23, 1938; 1.
      - John Seaman to Julius Emspak, September 1, 1938; 2.
      - Seaman to Emspak, October 3, 1938; 3.
      - Earl Fox to Emspak, October 14, 1938; 4.
      - Seaman to Emspak, November 1, 1938; 5.
      - Seaman to Emspak, December 2, 1938; 6.
      - Fox to UE, December 15, 1938; 7.
      - Fox to UE, December 30, 1938; 8.
      - Seaman to Emspak, January 3, 1939; 9.
      - Fox to UE, January 13, 1939; 10.
      - Seaman to Emspak, February 1, 1939; 11.
      - Seaman to Emspak, March 2, 1939; 12.
      - Fox to UE, March 31, 1939; 13.
      - Seaman to Emspak, April 4, 1939; 14.
      - Seaman to Emspak, May 2, 1939; 15.
      - Seaman to Emspak, June 5, 1939; 16.
      - Joseph Mitton to Emspak, June 29, 1939; 17.
      - Seaman to Emspak, July 7, 1939; 18.
      - Mitton Telegram to Emspak, August 9, 1939; 19.
      - Seaman to Emspak, August 9, 1939; 20.
      - Seaman to Emspak, September 1, 1939; 21-23.
      - Anthony Tusch to Emspak, September 13, 1939; 24.
      - Seaman to Emspak, October 3, 1939; 25.
      - Fox to Emspak, October 6, 1939; 26.
      - Fox to UE, October 27, 1939; 27.
      - Seaman to Emspak, November 3, 1939; 28.
      - Fox to Emspak, November 6, 1939; 29.
      - Seaman to Emspak, December 4, 1939; 30-31.
      - Seaman to Emspak, December 20, 1939; 32.
    - Local 103 Miscellaneous Financial Correspondence, 1940 and 1951 (Box 4, Folder 76)
      - John Seaman to Julius Emspak, January 2, 1940; 1.
      - Seaman to Emspak, January 5, 1940; 2.
      - Seaman to Emspak, January 29, 1940; 3.
      - Seaman to Emspak, February 2, 1940; 4.
      - Seaman to Emspak, March 1, 1940; 5.
      - Seaman to Emspak, April 1, 1940; 6.
      - Seaman to Emspak, May 2, 1940; 7.
      - Seaman to Emspak, May 10, 1940; 8.
      - Seaman to Emspak, June 4, 1940; 9-10.
      - Seaman to UE, June 21, 1940; 11.
      - Seaman to Emspak, July 3, 1940; 12-13.
      - Seaman to Emspak, July 12, 1940; 14.
      - Earl Fox to Emspak, July 22, 1940; 15.
      - Fox to Emspak, July 26, 1940; 16.
      - Seaman Telegram to Emspak, July 31, 1940; 17.
      - Seaman to Emspak, August 1, 1940; 18.
      - Seaman to Emspak, August 2, 1940; 19.
      - Fox to Emspak, August 5, 1940; 20.
      - Fox to Emspak, August 9, 1940; 21.
      - Fox to Emspak, August 16, 1940; 22.
      - Fox to Emspak, August 23, 1940; 23.
      - Emspak to Gene Derrickson, November 23, 1951; 24.
      - David Ratner Memo to H.J. Devlin, 25.
    - Local 103 Miscellaneous Financial Materials, 1940-1951 (Box 4, Folder 77)
      - Receipt, August 1, 1940; 1.
      - Samuel Basmajian W-4 Form, July 24, 1944; 2.
      - PAC Financial Report, 1946; 3.
      - Novelty Printing Company Bill, June 30, 1950; 4.
      - Financial Statement with Memo, November 1949 - June 1950; 5-6.
      - Financial Statement with Memo, 1950; 7.
      - Financial Statement, 1950; 8.
      - Financial Statement, 1949-1951; 9.
    - Local 103 Miscellaneous Financial Materials, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 78)
      - Third National Bank, Trust Company of Camden Regarding Failure to Pay Form with Checks from M.H. Goldstein and Morton Stavis, May 16, 1952; 1.
      - David Ratner to William Muloveen with January 18, 1956, Harold A. Hearn Letter to UE, January 24, 1956; 2.
    - Local 103 National Labor Relations Board Case No. 5-RC-461 and 5-RC-545, Order Remanding Proceeding to Regional Director, July 14, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Local 103 Mass Meeting Speeches, May 6, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Text of Speech by David Davis, 1.
      - Text of Speech by Russ Nixon, 2.
    - Local 103 Financial Meeting Minutes, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Local 103 Shop Talks Newspaper, 1942, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Local 103 News Bulletins, May 1 and July 19, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Local 103 Union Spotlight, June 1, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Local 103 Pamphlets, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - A Message to Philco Workers with January 27, 1949, Henry Rhine Letter to James Matles, 1.
      - $1000 Secret, 1949; 2.
      - To All Members of UE Local 103, July 14, 1950; 3.
    - Local 103 Leaflets, 1943-1950 (Box 4, Folder 86)
      - "Important", April 23, 1943; 1.
      - "Wage Agreements Reached", January 27, 1946; 2.
      - "The Facts About Basmajian", 1946-1947; 3.
      - "May 5th Newspapers Reports 23% More Profits for RCA", 1948; 4.
      - "UE Unity in Division 7 Wins $1294.03 Back Pay", 1950; 5.
    - Local 103 Newspaper Clippings, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Camden Courier Post, June 1, 1949; 1.
      - Camden Evening Courier, June 23, 1949; 2.
      - Camden Courier Post, April 25, 1951; 3.
    - Local 103 Arbitration, Alexander Giordano v. Radio Corporation of America et al., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Local 104
    - Local 104 Officer Lists, 1943-1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Dewitt Daubert to Julius Emspak, July 15, 1943; 1.
      - Earl Howell to Emspak, July 6, 1943; 2.
      - Officer List, September 20, 1944; 3.
      - Officer List, November 13, 1946; 4.
      - Officer List, April 26, 1947; 5.
      - Officer List, April 6, 1948; 6.
      - Officer List, October 11, 1948; 7.
      - William Tate to UE, December 1948; 8.
      - Officer List, January 18, 1949; 9.
    - Local 104 Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1948 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Carl Bersing to Earl Howell Regarding Overtime and War Mobilization Commission, January 11, 1944; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to John McDonough Regarding Sheridan Machine and Metropolitan Hinge Organization, May 17, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Howell Regarding Finances, May 21, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to McDonough Regarding Organization, May 21, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Harry Block Regarding Organization, May 21, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Howell Regarding Finances, June 15, 1943; 6.
      - Emspak to Carl Bersing, January 19, 1944; 7.
      - Emspak to Howell Regarding Factionalism, January 19, 1944; 8.
      - Emspak to Bersing with January 23, 1944, Howell Letter to Emspak, February 11, 1944; 9.
      - Emspak to Peter Besch Regarding Staff Members, March 28, 1945; 10.
      - Emspak to Howell Regarding Staff Members, March 28, 1945; 11.
      - Emspak to Howell Regarding Veterans and Finances, June 27, 1945; 12.
      - Emspak to Howell Regarding Local 104 Officers, April 23, 1947; 13.
      - Emspak to William Tate Regarding Finances, March 30, 1948; 14.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Howell Regarding Staff Members, April 25, 1944; 15.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to Howell Regarding Appointments, May 1, 1944; 16.
      - Fitzgerald to Howell Regarding Meetings, May 10, 1944; 17.
      - Fitzgerald to Howell Regarding Meetings, May 11, 1944; 18.
      - Fitzgerald Telegram to Howell Regarding Meetings, May 26, 1944; 19.
      - James Matles to Samuel Goldberg Regarding Dues, June 26, 1943; 20.
      - Matles to Howell Regarding Staff Members, September 25, 1943; 21.
    - Local 104 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Carl Bersing to Julius Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, February 14, 1944; 1.
      - Bersing to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, January 24, 1944; 2.
      - Samuel Goldberg to James Matles Regarding Local 104 Collective Bargaining, June 14, 1943; 3.
      - Goldberg to Robert Ney Regarding War Labor Board, December 22, 1943; 4.
      - Goldberg to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members, June 1, 1944; 5.
      - Earl Howell to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 15, 1943; 6.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, December 20, 1943; 7.
      - Howell to Bersing Regarding Overtime and War Labor Board, January 8, 1944; 8.
      - Howell to Bersing Regarding War Labor Board, January 12, 1944; 9.
      - Howell to Matles, January 13, 1944; 10.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, January 23, 1944; 11.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding Local 104 Sheridan Machine Contract, February 14, 1944; 12.
      - Howell to Fitzgerald Regarding War Labor Board, April 20, 1944; 13.
      - Howell to Fitzgerald Regarding War Labor Board, April 27, 1944; 14.
      - Howell to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, May 8, 1944; 15.
      - Howell to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, May 12, 1944; 16.
      - Howell to Fitzgerald Regarding Sheridan Machine Contract and War Labor Board, May 30, 1944; 17.
      - Howell Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding War Labor Board, May 1944; 18.
      - Howell to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, March 18, 1945; 19.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, April 24, 1945; 20-21.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding Finances and Veterans, June 23, 1945; 22.
    - Local 104 Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Earl Howell to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 104 Sheridan Machine Contracts, January 27, 1947; 1.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, February 9, 1947; 2.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, March 9, 1947; 3.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, April 6, 1947; 4.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding Local 104 Officers, April 7, 1947; 5.
      - Howell Telegram to UE Regarding Mailing List, April 18, 1947; 6.
      - Howell to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 19, 1947; 7.
      - Thomas O'Hare to UE Regarding Taft-Hartly and General Strike, May 8, 1947; 8.
      - William Tate to UE Regarding Finances, February 23, 1948; 9.
  - Local 105
    - Local 105 Officer Lists, 1944-1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Officer List, November 9, 1944; 1.
      - Officer List, February 24, 1948; 2.
      - Officer List, April 5, 1948; 3.
      - Officer List, August 24, 1948; 4.
      - Officer List, December 6, 1948; 5.
      - Officer List, March 17, 1949; 6.
      - Officer List, September 12, 1949; 7.
    - Local 105 Contract with January 25, 1943, Supplemental Agreement Number 11, July 29, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Local 105 Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Helen Bradford to Alice Flannery Regarding Local 105 International Resistor Company Contracts and Local 105 Constitutions, June 30, 1943; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to George Berry Regarding Supplies, October 19, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Finances, October 19, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Berry Regarding Supplies, November 2, 1938; 4.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Finances, March 27, 1939; 5.
      - Emspak to Berry Regarding Finances, April 7, 1939; 6.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Maytag Defense Fund, April 14, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to Berry Regarding Finances, April 26, 1939; 8.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Finances, June 16, 1939; 9.
      - Emspak to Local 105 Regarding Supplies, June 26, 1939; 10.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Finances, October 14, 1940; 11.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 12.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Mailing List, March 20, 1944; 13.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Finances and Veterans, March 20, 1945; 14.
      - Emspak to Flannery Regarding Finances and Veterans, June 1, 1945; 15.
      - Ray Klausner, Secretary of Albert Fitzgerald, to Peter Besch Regarding Letter, August 24, 1945; 16.
      - David Scribner to Berry Regarding Appointments, November 17, 1945; 17.
      - Scribner to Harry Block Regarding Local 105 International Resistor Contracts, December 12, 1945; 18.
    - Local 105 Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - George Berry to UE Regarding Supplies with Memo, October 13, 1938; 1.
      - Berry to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 28, 1938; 2.
      - Berry to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 28, 1939; 3.
      - Berry to David Scribner Regarding Appointment, November 13, 1945; 4.
      - Peter Besch to Ray Klausner Regarding War Labor Board, August 27, 1945; 5.
      - Harry Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and the Office of Price Adjustment, November 27, 1944; 6.
      - Block to Scribner Regarding War Labor Board, Wages, and Office of Price Adjustment, December 5, 1945; 7.
      - Joseph Bradford to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board and Local 105 International Register Contracts, November 9, 1944; 8.
      - Alice Flannery to UE Regarding Finances, September 20, 1938; 9.
      - Flannery to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 2, 1938; 10.
      - Flannery to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 8, 1938; 11.
      - Flannery to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 15, 1939; 12.
      - Flannery to UE Regarding Supplies, April 1, 1939; 13.
      - Flannery to UE Regarding Finances, September 15, 1939; 14.
      - Flannery to UE Regarding Supplies, June 6, 1939; 15.
      - Flannery to UE Regarding Supplies, July 10, 1939; 16.
      - Flannery to UE Regarding Finances, November 6, 1939; 17.
      - Flannery to UE Regarding Supplies, November 16, 1939; 18.
      - Flannery to Bradford Regarding Factionalism and Wages, July 2, 1943; 19.
      - Flannery to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, February 24, 1944; 20.
      - Flannery to UE Regarding Address Change, October 25, 1944; 21.
      - Flannery to Emspak Regarding Finances and Veterans, March 19, 1945; 22.
      - Flannery to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, May 22, 1945; 23.
      - Albert Riesel to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, December 10, 1947; 24.
      - Elizabeth Sweeny to UE Regarding Wages, August 23, 1945; 25.
      - Luther Welzel to Emspak Regarding 1946 UE Convention, August 21, 1946; 26.
      - Welzel to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 3, 1946; 27.
      - Welzel to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 31, 1946; 28.